AMRUTHA SINDHU CB

2.10 Years of experience in IT Service Industry with experience and exposure to Software Testing/Quality Assurance in organization that offers opportunity for my career development.

Excellent interpersonal and communication skills aligned with good thought leadership. Skilled in grasping the requirement, conceptualizing, developing and implementing solutions and collaborating closely with various teams and customer.

amrutha08sindhu@gmail.com

+91-8197014087





EDUCATION

- BE Computer Science (2014), KSSEM, Bengaluru
- Diploma in Computer Science(2011), K.S Polytechnic, Bengaluru
- SSLC (2008), BTL Vidya Vahini High School, Bengaluru

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Jira
- Test Rail
- SQL
- Eclipse
- Selenium WebDriver
- Java
- GitHub

CAREER

PENTACHROME TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD - BANGALORE, INDIA

QA ANALYST

Major accomplishments:

- Successfully performed Manual testing activities throughout the software development life cycle (SDLC) with a major focus on the Agile Model.
- Expertise in documenting the defects with high level of detail, accuracy and informative recreation steps using Jira.
- Proficiently executed a wide range of Blackbox testing types such as Functionality, Integration, System, Smoke, Adhoc, Acceptance, Compatibility, Performance, Usability, Globalization, Regression, Exploratory, Comparison, Recovery, and Reliability Testing.
- Managed the Defect Life Cycle, effectively tracking, reporting and resolving issues to maintain high quality standards.
- Developed comprehensive Test Cases and Test Plans, Test Scripts, Test Reviews ensuring thorough test coverage and providing clear guidelines for testing activities.
- Ability to Automate Web Application using Web Driver in Eclipse, involved in writing Xpath, locating the Elements using Locators, Handling different types of popups.

Experience in Non-Technical:

| May 2019 to Aug 2020, Pos | sitive Score Managemen | t Services, Tea | m Lead/Operation |
|---------------------------|------------------------|-----------------|------------------|
| Manager. | | | |

| $\ \square$ Analyze and improving the organizational process, Oversee the High-Level HR |
|---|
| duties, Supervising, Hiring, and train the employees. Work together to improve |
| quality, productivity, and efficiency. |

March 2015 to April 2019, Debt Doctor Management Services-Bangalore, Sr. Financial Consultant & Team Lead.

☐ Motivated team on both inbound and outbound calls, interacting with the clients and understanding their requirements and problems, ran monthly goal contests with rewards, Motivated staff to reach sales goals through contests and bonuses.

September 2014 to March 2015 Debt Doctor Management Services-Bangalore, Jr. Financial Consultant.

| $\hfill \square$ Interacting with the customers and explaining about CIBIL, | communicating with |
|---|--------------------|
| the clients face to face. | |

PROJECTS:

Project 1:

Project Name: HypeLog Processo

Duration: 1.6 years

Domain: Customer Analytics

Role: Manual Tester

Hype Log Processo it is a Hybrid application and the main aim of this project is to maintain data of the Customer Lead. The main activities covered are Creating Expo,

Creating Lead data, Converting Lead to Potential, Sales Order, Purchase Order and Invoice. This project maintains the records of a generating particular order invoice.

Project 2:

Project Name: Scarce Dime

Duration: 1.4 years **Domain:** HMS

Role: Manual and Automation Tester Scarce Dime is a Web application and one of the fast-growing healthcare centers, undergoes various upgrades to improve its business and to become one of the main providers of medical and surgical services to the residents at affordable charges. The main aim of this project is to maintain patient records, avoiding physical work of providing appointment for patients, uploading prescription, registration of patients, computerized billing in hospital and labs. This software has the facility to give a unique id for every patient and stores the details of every patient and the staff automatically

Java:

- Good Knowledge on OOPS Concepts, Methods, Operators.
- Abstract Class, Interface, Object Creation, Exception Handling.
- Static and its members, non-static and its members,
- Constructors, Constructor chaining.
- Knowledge on method overloading, method overriding.

API Testing:

- Very good knowledge on HTTP Methods.
- Good knowledge on validating different status codes like 200, 201,
- 400, 403, 404,422, 500 etc.
- Getting knowledge and learning from YouTube.
- Good understanding of SOAP and REST web service testing.

Database (SQL):

- Good understanding of RDBMS concepts like Constraints, Datatypes etc.
- Good understanding of SQL concepts like Sub-Queries, Functions etc..
- Good knowledge in Table creation, insertion and deletion.
- Good knowledge in single row and multirow functions.

Declaration:

I do here by declare that all the information provided above in the resume is true, complete and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Yours Sincerely, Amrutha sindhu CB